Enkhdavaa Batlkhagva



a batlkhagva.e@gmail.com

dave-bat.vercel.app 🔘 @enkhdavaa 📊 Enkhdavaa Batlkhagva

I am a software engineer with 5 years of experience in developing software applications. I have worked with Thermo Fisher Scientific and ICT Netherlands, where I gained experience working in agile/safe scrum teams. I am proficient in C# and C++ programming languages and have a keen interest in working with the .NET ecosystem and DevOps.

Experience

Software Developer

Thermo Fisher Scientific

October 2021 — Present

Eindhoven, NL

- Created C# and C++ adapters to bridge divergent
- Integrated Model-Based testing (MBT) with the DevOps infrastucture.
- Investigated the tool and created a development process for MBT.
- Created state transition models for testing various systems.

.NET C#, C++, Jenkins, Scripting

Software Designer

ICT Netherlands B.V.

☐ Jan 2021 — Present

Q Eindhoven, NL

- Developed an C# OPC-UA API.
- Developed a 3D virtual hardware simulator for testing control software.
- Automated build and deployment (CI/CD) for the simulator
- UI feature improvements on AR Hololens.

.NET C#, Docker, Unity 3D

Software Designer Trainee

Thermo Fisher Scientific

☐ Jan 2020 — Oct 2020

Eindhoven, NL

• Designed and developed a proof of concept for 3D virtual hardware simulator tool. The tool is for testing software using Unity3D game engine.

.NET C#, Unity 3D, Matlab

Software Engineer

Tavan Bogd Management

☐ Mar 2018 — Sep 2018

Ulaanbaatar, MNG

- Collected requirements for data transfer application.
- Developed a Windows Form Application for transfering an excel data to DB.

.NET C#, C

Education

Engineering Doctorate (EngD) in Software **Technology**

Eindhoven University of Technology

Oct 2018 — Oct 2020

Eindhoven, NL

Projects

Model Based Testing (MBT)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

Oct 2021 — Present

Eindhoven, NL

- · Developed state transition models for random test generation
- Created a testing workflow for development process
- Developed adapters for CI by connecting SUT with MBT
- Created documentations and presentations for users

Axini, .NET C#, C++, GIT, Jenkins, Shell scripting

Center Of Excellence (COE)

ICT Netherlands B.V.

☐ Jan 2021 — Oct 2022

Eindhoven, NL

- Designed and developed a virtual 3D factory simulator to replace hardware testing dependency
- · Developed HAL interface for the simulator (DT) for higher abstraction layer software
- Created CI & CD for the simulator (DT)

Unity3D, OPC-UA, .NET C#, GIT, Docker, Bamboo CI

Virtual Hardware Simulator for Transmission **Electron Microscope (EngD)**

Thermo Fisher Scientific

☐ Jan 2020 — Oct 2020

Eindhoven, NL

• Deisgned and implemented a 3D virtual hardware simulator for firmware and software testing so that testing is not dependent on real hardware.

Unity3D, .NET C#, GIT, Matlab, Docker

Dependency Management and Scope Control for HMI products (EngD)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

Sep 2019 — Dec 2019

Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Codeveloped a domain-specific language and a livecode dependency checker to detect software architechture

Role: Software engineer co-developing a live dependency checker

Roslyn, .NET C#

For more projects next page ...

Skills

Agile Scrum
Git
C#
C++
JavaScript
Python

Hobby

- Bouldering, Improvization, Running
- Playing guitar, sketching
- Game development

Projects

Designing Smart Landing System for Agricultural Drones (EngD)

AgroTech

☐ May 2019 — Jul 2019

P Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Design and implement the drone control software to save time of field analytics

Role: CI engineer and software engineer, responsible for proposing design choices and co-developing the drone control

Python, DroneKit

Face AI for Condition Monitoring (EngD)

Philips Healthcare

□ Jan 2019 — Apr 2019

Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Add new features to the existing remote consultation system using AI services (Microsoft face AI, Amazon Rekognition)

Role: Software developer/Configuration manager responsible for co-developing back-end services using C# and implementing a CI pipeline

Microsoft Face AI, Amazon rekognition, .NET C#